Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - T-Z
        - Tony! Toni! Toné! - The blues, 1990; SR-29105; Tony! Toni! Toné! (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29104. 2 copies.
        - Tony! Toni! Toné! - The revival, 1990; SR-29106; Tony! Toni! Toné! (Box 75)
          Catalog # 841 902-1; A-side Matrix # DMM 422841902-1-AS-SP-DMM DMS SP1-1
        - Tony! Toni! Toné! - Oakland stroke (the remixes), 1990; SR-29107; Tony! Toni! Toné! (Box 75)
          Catalog # WINXR 7; A-side Matrix # WINXR 7 A-1U-1-1
        - Tony! Toni! Toné! - Oakland stroke, 1990; SR-29108; Tony! Toni! Toné! (Box 75)
          Catalog # WINGX 7; A-side Matrix # WINGX 7 A-1U-1-1
        - Too Kool Posse - Give'em a sample; Do you wanna get hype, 1988; SR-29109; Too Kool Posse (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29110
          Catalog # PRO-7231-DJ; A-side Matrix # A-1 PRO-7231-A H
          Profile Records
        - Too Kool Posse - Give'em a sample; Do you wanna get hype, 1988; SR-29110; Too Kool Posse (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29109
        - Toots & The Maytals - Pass the pipe, 1979; SR-29111; Toots & The Maytals (Box 75)
          Catalog # MLPS-9534; A-side Matrix # A-1 MLPS-9534-A
          Mango
        - Top Billin' - My thing, 1989; SR-29112; Top Billin' (Box 75)
          Catalog # DOPTR DJ 4; A-side Matrix # DOPTR 4 A-1J-1-1 STO
          Rap Sonic
        - Torch Song - Don't look now, 1987; SR-29113; Torch Song (Box 75)
          Catalog # L33-17308; A-side Matrix # IRS 6739 AM1 2
          I.R.S. Records
        - Total Contrast - Beat to beat, 1987; SR-29114; Total Contrast (Box 75)
          Catalog # 828 068-1 R-1; A-side Matrix # 422-828-068-1-AS-SP 1-1
          London Records
        - Toto - Hydra, 1979; SR-29115; Toto (Box 75)
          Catalog # FC 36229; A-side Matrix # PAL 36229-1E
        - Toto - Georgy porgy (special disco remix), 1979; SR-29116; Toto (Box 75)
          Catalog # AS 637; A-side Matrix # XSS-165962-1C
        - Toto - Toto IV sampler, 1983; SR-29117; Toto (Box 75)
          Catalog # AS 1645; A-side Matrix # P XSM 169271-1A
        - Touch - Me and you; Energizer, 1977; SR-29118; Touch (Box 75)
          Catalog # DISCO 208; A-side Matrix # 7-977 JR
        - Touch Of Class - Touch Of Class, 1979; SR-29119; Touch Of Class (Box 75)
          Catalog # BXL1-3217; A-side Matrix # BXL1 3217 A 1 A F
          Roadshow
        - Toulouse - Toulouse, 1977; SR-29120; Toulouse (Box 75)
          Catalog # IM 304; A-side Matrix # MAG-1010A-3 TLC IM-304-A
          Image Records
        - Touré Kunda - Touré Kunda, 1982; SR-29121; Touré Kunda (Box 75)
          Catalog # CEL 6599; A-side Matrix # CEL 6599 A
          Celluloid
        - Tower Of Power - Rock baby, 1979; SR-29122; Tower Of Power (Box 75)
          Catalog # AS 632; A-side Matrix # XSS 165950-1C
        - Townshend, Fuzz - Tasty big Ed, 1998; SR-29123; Townshend, Fuzz (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29124. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ECDJ531; A-side Matrix # ECDJ 531 A-1-1-
          Echo
        - Townshend, Fuzz - Tasty big Ed, 1998; SR-29124; Townshend, Fuzz (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29123. 2 copies.
        - Toyan - Spar with me, 1982; SR-29125; Toyan (Box 75)
          Catalog # VPRLP 1010; A-side Matrix # VPRD 1010-A
          Jah Guidance
          Jamaica, New York
        - Traffic - On the road, 1973; SR-29126; Traffic (Box 75)
          Catalog # SMAS-9336; A-side Matrix # SMAS-1-9336 212
        - Trammps - Slipping out, 1980; SR-29127; Trammps (Box 75)
          Catalog # SD 19290; A-side Matrix # ST-A 804591-A 0-1 SM1-2 SP FWQ
        - Trammps - Disco inferno, 1976; SR-29128; Trammps (Box 75)
          Catalog # SD 18211; A-side Matrix # ST-A-76377913 SIDE A-RE1 (PR) TM/JR
        - Travis, Erik - Work it, bounce it, 2001; SR-29129; Travis, Erik (Box 75)
          Catalog # ET 16; A-side Matrix # ET-016-A HOT WAXX
          F.A.C.T. Records
        - Trey Max - Top secret beats volume I, 1992; SR-29130; Trey Max (Box 75)
          Catalog # MRLP-55007; A-side Matrix # MRLP-55007-A
          Freeze Records
        - Triad - Look into your eyes, 1995; SR-29131; Triad (Box 75)
          Catalog # EX-IT 205; A-side Matrix # EXT-205-A MAMI TAPE UX US NC of
          Ex-It Records
        - Tribe Called Quest - People's instictive travels and the paths of rhythm, 1990; SR-29132; Tribe Called Quest (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29133. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1331-1-J; A-side Matrix # SM1 13311 JA 20 DMS Ȼ
          Jive
        - Tribe Called Quest - People's instictive travels and the paths of rhythm, 1990; SR-29133; Tribe Called Quest (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29132. 2 copies.
        - Tricky - Makes me wanna die, 1997; SR-29134; Tricky (Box 75)
          Catalog # 12 BRW 348; A-side Matrix # EX 12 BRW 348 A1 DF1 97-3
          4th & Broadway
        - Tricky - Pre-millennium tension, 1996; SR-29135; Tricky (Box 75)
          Catalog # BRLP 623; A-side Matrix # BRLP 623-A1
        - Trinidad Bill - Hardness is badness, 1981; SR-29136; Trinidad Bill (Box 75)
          Catalog # BT 1003; A-side Matrix # BTLP-1003-A
          Sparrow's Hideaway
        - Trinidad Troubadors - Constant fete, 1976; SR-29137; Trinidad Troubadors; Ricardo, Tony; Qualis, Bob; Larry D (Box 75)
          Catalog # GS 8890; A-side Matrix # GS-8890 A
          Strakers Recording
        - Trinity - Have a little faith, 1980; SR-29138; Trinity (Box 75)
          Catalog # MICCAN 0023; A-side Matrix # MICCAN 0023-A TLC
          Micron Music Limited
          Canada
        - Trinity - African revolution, 1980; SR-29139; Trinity (Box 75)
          Catalog # GG0020LP; A-side Matrix # DSR 9929 A DT TRINITY LP GG
          GG's Records
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Trinity - Rock in the ghetto, 1979; SR-29140; Trinity (Box 75)
          Catalog # TRLS 170; A-side Matrix # BILBO AL1 S-2 TRLS 170A-1
          Trojan Records
        - Trio - Trio, 1982; SR-29141; Trio (Box 75)
          Catalog # MX-1-509; A-side Matrix # MX 1509AS-PRC-C-1-1-1
        - Triplets - Break the silence, 1986; SR-29142; Triplets (Box 75)
          Catalog # 60455-1-Y; A-side Matrix # STE 60455 A-1 1-1
        - Troiano - We all need love, 1979; SR-29143; Troiano (Box 75)
          Catalog # 8518; A-side Matrix # S33-95553 G-1 1-8518
        - Troop - Attitude, 1989; SR-29144; Troop (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29145. Different discs.
          Catalog # 82035-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-897581-A 1-1
        - Afrika Bambaataa - Soca fever (rock it); Electro funk express, 1991; SR-29145; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29144. Different discs.
          Catalog # DFC 047; A-side Matrix # DFC 047-I 0
          DFC
        - Troop - Troop, 1988; SR-29146; Troop (Box 75)
          Catalog # 81851-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-886893-B 1-1
        - Trouble Funk - E flat boogie, 2000; SR-29147; Trouble Funk (Box 75)
          Catalog # DEL LP 0030; A-side Matrix # DEL-LP-0030-A E FLAT BOOGIE
          Funky Delicacies
        - True Culture - It's so good, it's bad, 1991; SR-29148; True Culture (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29149. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 3-4017-0-DJ; A-side Matrix # 3-4017-0-DJ GOOD SIDE 1-1
          Cardiac Records
        - True Culture - It's so good, it's bad, 1991; SR-29149; True Culture (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29148. 2 copies.
        - True Love - I'm bustin'out, 1988; SR-29150; True Love (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29151. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 90940-1; A-side Matrix # ST-CR-886901-A 1-1
          Critique
          Woburn, Massachusetts
        - True Love - I'm bustin'out, 1988; SR-29151; True Love (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29150. 2 copies.
        - True Mathematics - I don't love you anymore, 1989; SR-29152; True Mathematics (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29153. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FMS 62338; A-side Matrix # SelEct FMS-62338A F/W HuB
          Select Records
        - True Mathematics - I don't love you anymore, 1989; SR-29153; True Mathematics (Box 75)
          In same jacket as # SR-29152. 2 copies.
        - True Mathematics - Greatest hits, 1988; SR-29154; True Mathematics (Box 75)
          Catalog # SEL21626; A-side Matrix # A-1 SEL-21626-A HERbIE JR
        - True Solace - Thank you, 1999; SR-29155; True Solace (Box 75)
          Catalog # DMD 2518; A-side Matrix # STDM-89366-89367-1 p/m RCF
        - Tube - There and then EP, 1999; SR-29156; Tube (Box 75)
          Catalog # JSK 144; A-side Matrix # JSK-144A-1A RJ
          Jungle Sky
        - Tubeway Army - First album, 1979; SR-29157; Tubeway Army (Box 75)
          Catalog # SD 32-106; A-side Matrix # ST-C-814708-A Ct4P SP 0-2 SM 2-1
          ATCO Records
        - Tucker, Junior - Take a message, 1980; SR-29158; Tucker, Junior (Box 75)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # DSR-1856-A-DT Tuff Gong
          Tuff Gong
        - Tucker, Junior - It's a small, small world, 1978; SR-29164; Tucker, Junior (Box 75)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # TC DSR 8840 A DT
          Top Ranking
        - Marshall Tucker Band - Running like the wind, 1979; SR-29159; Marshall Tucker Band (Box 76)
          Catalog # BSK 3317; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3317 LW1
        - Tudes - I hear my heart beat, 1992; SR-29160; Tudes (Box 76)
          Catalog # CMP 1302; A-side Matrix # CMP 1302 U F/W
          Cachet Entertainment
        - Tuff City Squad - Breakmania 4, 1993; SR-29161; Tuff City Squad (Box 76)
          Catalog # TUF LP 0580; A-side Matrix # TUF LP 0580-A
          Tuff City
        - Tuff City Squad - Beats for jeeps, 1992; SR-29162; Tuff City Squad (Box 76)
          Catalog # TUF LP 0578; A-side Matrix # TUF LP 578 A
        - Ike & Tina Turner - The hunter, 1969; SR-29163; Ike & Tina Turner (Box 76)
          Catalog # BTS-8811; A-side Matrix # BTS-1-8811-1-A7 BTS11-A-S021
          Blue Thumb Records
        - Turner, Spyder - Only love, 1980; SR-29165; Turner, Spyder (Box 76)
          Catalog # WHK 3397; A-side Matrix # WHK-1-3397 LW3 3
          Whitfield Records
        - Turrentine, Stanley - Tender togetherness, 1981; SR-29166; Turrentine, Stanley (Box 76)
          Catalog # 5E-534; A-side Matrix # ll + SP SLM + 0-1 SM 1-2 837 5E-531 A 1 SH-SP F3
        - Twennynine - All I want, 1981; SR-29167; Twennynine; White, Lenny (Box 76)
          Catalog # AS-11539; A-side Matrix # AS-11539 A/SP F2 + SP SLM + 0-1 SM1-1 1043
        - Twennynine - Best of friends, 1979; SR-29168; Twennynine; White, Lenny (Box 76)
          Catalog # 6E-223 SP; A-side Matrix # 1-2 6E-223-A-2 SP F3
        - Twennynine - Peanut butter; Citi dancin', 1979; SR-29169; Twennynine; White, Lenny (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29170. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AS-11432; A-side Matrix # ASS 11432 A-1 SP
        - Twennynine - Peanut butter; Citi dancin', 1979; SR-29170; Twennynine; White, Lenny (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29169. 2 copies.
        - Twista - Twista celebooty; Ludacross (remixes), 2004; SR-29171; Twista; Trina; Ludacris (Box 76)
          Catalog # CAR 003; A-side Matrix # CAR-003-A1
          Cut & Run
        - Two Man Sound - Que tal America, 1979; SR-29172; Two Man Sound (Box 76)
          Catalog # JDC 12-4; A-side Matrix # JDC-12-4-A AZ J
          JDC Records
          Marina Del Rey, California
        - Two Tons - Backatcha, 1980; SR-29173; Two Tons; Two Tons O' Fun (Box 76)
          Catalog # F-9605; A-side Matrix # F 9605 A-1B S1 SX
          Fantasy Honey Records
        - Two Tons O' Fun - Two Tons O' Fun, 1980; SR-29174; Two Tons O' Fun (Box 76)
          Catalog # F-9584; A-side Matrix # XS 5 F9584 A RE1-1A JGS
        - Tyree - I fear the night, 1986; SR-29175; Tyree; Cooper, Tyree; Chic (Box 76)
          Catalog # UN 103; A-side Matrix # UN-103-A -pa-586
          Underground
        - U-Roy - Dread in a Babylon, 1975; SR-29176; U-Roy (Box 76)
          Catalog # PZ 34234; A-side Matrix # AL-34234-1B
          Virgin
        - UB40 - Geffery Morgan..., 1984; SR-29177; UB40 (Box 76)
          Catalog # LP DEP 6; A-side Matrix # LPDEP 6 A-1U-1-1-1 TOWNHOUSE
          DEP International
          Birmingham, England
        - UB40 - Baggariddim, 1985; SR-29178; UB40 (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29179. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LP DEP 10C; A-side Matrix # LFDEP 10 A-1U-1-1- TOWNHOUSE
        - UB40 - Baggariddim, 1985; SR-29179; UB40 (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29178. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LP DEP 10C; A-side Matrix # LFDEP 10 C-1U-1-5-3 TOWNHOUSE
        - UBC - 2 all serious thinkers, 1990; SR-29180; UBC (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29181. 2 copies.
          Catalog # E1-93919; A-side Matrix # E1-1-93919-21 DMM DMS HERbIE JR SP 1-1
        - UBC - 2 all serious thinkers, 1990; SR-29181; UBC (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29180. 2 copies.
        - Uberzone And Rennie Pilgrem - Black widow, 2000; SR-29182; Uberzone And Rennie Pilgrem (Box 76)
          Catalog # RENN3042; A-side Matrix # RENN 3042 A-1-1-1 THE EXCHANGE-NiLZ
          Thursday Club Recordings (TCR)
          London, England
        - UFO - Volume 2, 1996; SR-29183; UFO (Box 76)
          Catalog # PBLR 5; A-side Matrix # PBLR 5 A-1-1-I
          Penny Black
        - Ullanda - Want ads, 1979; SR-29184; Ullanda (Box 76)
          Catalog # OR 7500; A-side Matrix # OR 7500-AS-LON9-CSM-2 OMP
          Ocean Ariola America
        - Ullanda - Love zone, 1979; SR-29185; Ullanda (Box 76)
          Catalog # OR 49900; A-side Matrix # 1 5 OR 49900 AS-1A A-4
        - Ultramagnetic MC's - Critical beatdown, 1988; SR-29186; Ultramagnetic MC's (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29187. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PL-1013; A-side Matrix # PL-1013A F/W CSB FF 1-1
          Next Plateau Records Inc.
        - Ultramagnetic MC's - Critical beatdown, 1988; SR-29187; Ultramagnetic MC's (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29186. 2 copies.
        - Ultramagnetic MC's - The b-sides companion, 1997; SR-29188; Ultramagnetic MC's (Box 76)
          Catalog # NPE 5482-1; A-side Matrix # NPE-5482-1A HLBTL
          Next Plateau Entertainment
        - Ultramagnetic MC's - New York what is funky, 1996; SR-29189; Ultramagnetic MC's (Box 76)
          Catalog # OSF LP 4021; A-side Matrix # 4021-A THE ULTRAMAGNETIC MCS
          Ol' Skool Flava
        - Ultravox - Rage in Eden, 1981; SR-29190; Ultravox (Box 76)
          Catalog # CHR 1338; A-side Matrix # 15 CHR-1338-AS Sm-5 SX CB
          Chrysalis
        - Ultravox - Thin wall, 1981; SR-29191; Ultravox (Box 76)
          Catalog # CHS 122 540; A-side Matrix # 634 A POLYGRAM CHC 122540 2 AV TOWN HOUSE
        - Ultravox - Vienna, 1981; SR-29192; Ultravox (Box 76)
          Catalog # CHS 12 2481; A-side Matrix # CHS-12-2481-AS PRC-C-1-1-1 CB
        - Ultravox - All stood still, 1981; SR-29193; Ultravox (Box 76)
          Catalog # CHS-2522-PDJ; A-side Matrix # CHS-2522-PDJ-AS CP-1
        - Under 99 - Free to be, 1991; SR-29194; Under 99 (Box 76)
          Catalog # WHOLE 91250; A-side Matrix # WH 91250 A
          Whole Records
        - Underground - Behind my back; Doin' it, 1981; SR-29195; Underground (Box 76)
          Catalog # S-12341; A-side Matrix # K13217 CCL S-12341-3
          Sam Records
        - Underground - Beaucoup fish (disc one), 1999; SR-29196; Underground (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29197. Double album.
          Catalog # JBO1005431; A-side Matrix # JBO 1005431 A-3-1-1
          Junior Boy's Own
        - Underground - Beaucoup fish (disc two), 1999; SR-29197; Underground (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29196. Double album.
          Catalog # JBO1005431; A-side Matrix # JBO 1005431 C-3-1-1
        - Undisputed Truth - Down to earth, 1974; SR-29198; Undisputed Truth (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29199. 2 copies.
          Catalog # G6-968S1; A-side Matrix # G6-96831-D5RS-77091 13A
        - Undisputed Truth - Down to earth, 1974; SR-29199; Undisputed Truth (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29198. 2 copies.
          Catalog # G6-968S1; A-side Matrix # G6-96831-D5RS-7709-1 12A
        - Undisputed Truth - Cosmic truth, 1975; SR-29200; Undisputed Truth (Box 76)
          Catalog # G6-970S1; A-side Matrix # G6970S1-E5RS-7516-1-RE1-S-03B #12
        - Unlimited Touch - Searching to find the one, 1981; SR-29201; Unlimited Touch (Box 76)
          Catalog # PRL D 529; A-side Matrix # PRLD-529-A FW FK/HP
        - Unlimited Touch - Unlimited Touch, 1981; SR-29202; Unlimited Touch (Box 76)
          Catalog # PRL 12184; A-side Matrix # PRL-12184-A FW HERb
        - Unlimited Touch - Yes, we're ready, 1983; SR-29203; Unlimited Touch (Box 76)
          Catalog # PRL 14108; A-side Matrix # A- PRL-14108-AS ANgiE HERbIE JR
        - Up, Bustle And Out - The revolutionary woman of the windmill (remixes), 1996; SR-29204; Up, Bustle And Out (Box 76)
          Catalog # ZEN 1241; A-side Matrix # MPO ZEN 1241 A1 THE EXCHANGE-NiLZ
          Ninja Tune
        - Urang Otan - Urang Otan, 1981; SR-29205; Urang Otan (Box 76)
          Catalog # ZOAR 06; A-side Matrix # ZOAR-6-A
          Zoar Records
        - Urban Verbs - Early damage, 1981; SR-29206; Urban Verbs (Box 76)
          Catalog # BSK 3533; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3533-LW1
        - Ursull, Joelle - Miyel, 1988; SR-29207; Ursull, Joelle (Box 76)
          Catalog # CBS 462433 1; A-side Matrix # t 462433-2 A1
          Netherlands
        - U.T.F.O. - Skeezer pleezer, 1986; SR-29208; U.T.F.O. (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29209; SR-29210. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SEL 21616; A-side Matrix # A- SEL-21616-A F/W HERbIE JR '' I STILL DON'T HAVE A JACKET'' DOC+MiX!!
        - U.T.F.O. - Skeezer pleezer, 1986; SR-29209; U.T.F.O. (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29208; SR-29210. 2 copies.
        - U.T.F.O. - Split personality, 1986; SR-29210; U.T.F.O. (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29208; SR-29209. Different discs.
          Catalog # FMS 62276; A-side Matrix # HERbIE JR ANgiE '' Yo DOC, I CAN'T FIND MY JACKET MAYBE ''Mix'' HAS IT'' ''This 12'' Is DOPE, IT'S STUPId FRESH; IT'S ROCKEd BY THE PUMP'' FMS-62276-A
        - Valentin, Dave - Pied piper, 1981; SR-29211; Valentin, Dave (Box 76)
          Catalog # GRP 5505; A-side Matrix # 0 GRP 5505 SA CP2
          Arista GRP
        - Valli, Frankie - Heaven above me, 1980; SR-29212; Valli, Frankie (Box 76)
          Catalog # MCA-5134; A-side Matrix # MCA-2233-ML1 TML-S
        - Valli, Frankie - Inside you, 1975; SR-29213; Valli, Frankie (Box 76)
          Catalog # M6-852S1; A-side Matrix # M6-852S1-HS-2527-1-S-03B #13
        - Valli, Frankie - Reunited live (disc one), 1980; SR-29214; Valli, Frankie; 4 Seasons (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29215. Double album.
          Catalog # 2WB 3497; A-side Matrix # 2WB-1-3497-WW1
        - Valli, Frankie - Reunited live (disc two), 1980; SR-29215; Valli, Frankie; 4 Seasons (Box 76)
          In same jacket as # SR-29214. Double album.
        - Valli, Frankie - The very best of, 1979; SR-29216; Valli, Frankie (Box 76)
          Catalog # MCA-3198; A-side Matrix # MCA-2050-ML2
        - Vallot, Pascal - Pascal Vallot, 1988; SR-29217; Vallot, Pascal (Box 77)
          Catalog # 8385-17; A-side Matrix # 8385-17 A
          Tropic Production
        - Van Dyke, Earl - The Earl of funk, 1970; SR-29218; Van Dyke, Earl (Box 77)
          Catalog # HS-1740; A-side Matrix # SS-715 HS-1739-2 S-1 J1 6-4 70 Z4RS-3058-1 D
          Soul
        - Vandross, Luther - Bad boy-Having a party, 1982; SR-29219; Vandross, Luther (Box 77)
          Catalog # AS 1547; A-side Matrix # XSS-170346-1A
        - Vandross, Luther - Forever for always for love, 1982; SR-29220; Vandross, Luther (Box 77)
          Catalog # FE 38235; A-side Matrix # AL38235-1B
        - Vaness, Theo - Theo Vaness, 1979; SR-29221; Vaness, Theo (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29222. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRL 12173; A-side Matrix # P RL 12173A-1B
        - Vaness, Theo - Theo Vaness, 1979; SR-29222; Vaness, Theo (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29221. 2 copies.
        - Vanity 6 - Vanity 6, 1982; SR-29223; Vanity 6 (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29224. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1-23716; A-side Matrix # 1-23716-A-S2 B-16918 A S2 + SLM 1976
        - Vanity 6 - Vanity 6, 1982; SR-29224; Vanity 6 (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29223. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1-23716; A-side Matrix # 1-23716-A-SR-2 +1
        - Vanucci, Aldo - Aldo Vanucci, 2002; SR-29225; Vanucci, Aldo (Box 77)
          Test pressing
          Catalog # UPT 001; A-side Matrix # UPT 001 A
        - Variations - Moroccan roll, 1974; SR-29226; Variations (Box 77)
          Catalog # BDS-5601; A-side Matrix # BDS-5601-A SON
          Buddah Records
        - Veal, Charles - Believe it, 1981; SR-29227; Veal, Charles (Box 77)
          Catalog # ST-12174; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12194F5
        - Ventures - The Ventures in space, 1978; SR-29228; Ventures (Box 77)
          Catalog # SPC 3604; A-side Matrix # A-2 SPC-3604A TR CR1/78
          Pickwick
          Minneapolis, Minnesota
        - Vericheri - Ultra-sonic breakdance, 1983; SR-29229; Vericheri (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29230. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ZK 131; A-side Matrix # FW/NY ZK-131-A
          Zakia Records
        - Vericheri - Ultra-sonic breakdance, 1983; SR-29230; Vericheri (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29229. 2 copies.
        - Verlaine, Tom - Dreamtime, 1981; SR-29231; Verlaine, Tom (Box 77)
          Catalog # BSK 3539; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3539 JW1
        - Vibe - Confessions (disc one), 1999; SR-29232; Vibe (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29233. Double album.
          Catalog # 524 666-1; A-side Matrix # DFI 99 52 4 66-1 A =0=
          Universal
        - Vibe - Confessions (disc two), 1999; SR-29233; Vibe (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29232. Double album.
          Catalog # 524 666-1; A-side Matrix # DFI-9 9-4 524666-1 C =0=
        - Vicious Four - Hard rap, 1986; SR-29234; Vicious Four (Box 77)
          Catalog # NP50044; A-side Matrix # NP 50044 A
        - Vieira, Joey D. - Drumdrops volume one, 1978; SR-29235; Vieira, Joey D. (Box 77)
          Catalog # DD-7777; A-side Matrix # DD 7777 SIDE 1-RE 22150 (2)
          Music Tree Corporation
          Whipple, Georgia
        - View To The Future - Purity, 1997; SR-29236; View To The Future (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29237. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 74321 49802 1; A-side Matrix # 743-214 980 21-A 7432 1498021-A
          Alphakid Recordings
        - View To The Future - Purity, 1997; SR-29237; View To The Future (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29236. 2 copies.
        - Village People - Can't stop the music-the original soundtrack album, 1980; SR-29238; Village People (Box 77)
          Catalog # NBLP 7220; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7220-AS P AZ
        - Village People - 5 o'clock in the morning, 1981; SR-29239; Village People (Box 77)
          Catalog # JD-12259; A-side Matrix # A1 JD-12259-A1
        - Village People - Renaissance, 1981; SR-29240; Village People (Box 77)
          Catalog # AFL1-4105; A-side Matrix # AFL1-4105-A-3 A2G
        - Village People - In the navy; Manhattan woman, 1979; SR-29241; Village People (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29242. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NBD 20155 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20155 AS-1CP
        - Village People - In the navy; Manhattan woman, 1979; SR-29242; Village People (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29241. 2 copies.